<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog Page Template</title>
    <link>http://www.example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blog Page Template</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:48:24 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atlanta Braves</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/atlanta-braves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:48:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/atlanta-braves/</guid>
      <description>1966&amp;ndash;1974[edit]

An away jersey worn by Hank Aaron in 1969.
The Braves were a .500 team in their first few years in Atlanta; 85&amp;ndash;77 in 1966, 77&amp;ndash;85 in 1967, and 81&amp;ndash;81 in 1968. The 1967 season was the Braves&#39; first losing season since 1952, their last year in Boston. In 1969, with the onset of divisional play, the Braves won the first-ever National League West Division title, before being swept by the &amp;ldquo;Miracle Mets&amp;rdquo; in the National League Championship Series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Milwaukee Braves</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/milwaukee-braves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:48:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/milwaukee-braves/</guid>
      <description>Milwaukee went wild over the Braves, drawing a then-NL record 1.8 million fans. The Braves finished 92&amp;ndash;62 in their first season in Milwaukee. The success of the relocated team showed that baseball could succeed in new markets, and the Philadelphia Athletics, St. Louis Browns, Brooklyn Dodgers, and New York Giants left their hometowns within the next five years.


Milwaukee Braves cap logo
As the 1950s progressed, the reinvigorated Braves became increasingly competitive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boston Braves</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/projects/boston-braves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:47:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/projects/boston-braves/</guid>
      <description>King Kelly cigarette card (Goodwin &amp;amp; Company, 1888)
The Cincinnati Red Stockings, established in 1869 as the first openly all-professional baseball team, voted to dissolve after the 1870 season. Player-manager Harry Wright, with brother George and two other Cincinnati players, then went to Boston, Massachusetts at the invitation of Boston Red Stockings founder Ivers Whitney Adams to form the nucleus of the Boston Red Stockings, a charter member of the National Association of Professional Base Ball Players (NAPBBP).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Resturant at the End of the Universe</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/posts/this-is-also-a-slug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:13:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/posts/this-is-also-a-slug/</guid>
      <description>In The Restaurant at the End of the Universe (published in 1980), Zaphod is separated from the others and finds he is part of a conspiracy to uncover who really runs the Universe. Zaphod meets Zarniwoop, a conspirator and editor for The Guide, who knows where to find the secret ruler. Zaphod becomes briefly reunited with the others for a trip to Milliways, the restaurant of the title. Zaphod and Ford decide to steal a ship from there, which turns out to be a stunt ship pre-programmed to plunge into a star as a special effect in a stage show.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Hitchhiker&#39;s Guide to the Galaxy</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/posts/this-is-called-a-slug/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jul 2021 16:13:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/posts/this-is-called-a-slug/</guid>
      <description>The first book was adapted from the first four radio episodes (the Primary Phase), with Arthur being rescued from Earth&amp;rsquo;s destruction by Ford, meeting Zaphod and Trillian, coming to the planet of Magrathea to discover the true purpose of Earth, and ending with the group preparing to go to the Restaurant at the End of the Universe. It was first published in 1979, initially in paperback, by Pan Books, after BBC Publishing had turned down the offer of publishing a novelization, an action they would later regret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.example.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jul 2021 19:57:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.example.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Aubie&amp;rsquo;s existence began as a cartoon character that first appeared on the Auburn/Hardin-Simmons football program cover on October 3, 1959. Birmingham Post-Herald artist Phil Neel created the cartoon Tiger who continued to adorn Auburn program covers for 18 years.
Aubie&amp;rsquo;s look on the programs changed through the years. In 1962, he began to stand upright and the next year, 1963, he wore clothes for the first time (a blue tie and straw hat).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
